arbitrageconspiracy.com 2010-12-12

# Arbitrage Conspiracy Unleashed : Privacy-policy

**PRIVACY POLICY  
 **

**ARBITRAGECONSPIRACY.COM AND MIDDLEMANSYSTEM.COM IS A VENTURE OWNED AND OPERATED BY GREAT ERA HOLDINGS LTD. IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, THE WORDS "WE," "US," AND "OUR" REFER TO OUR COMPANY. THE WORDS "YOU," "YOUR," AND "YOURS" REFER TO YOU AND YOUR BUSINESS.**

**1\. How We Protect Your Privacy.**

This privacy policy tells you how we collect, use, and protect your personal information at www.ArbitrageConspiracy.com and www.MiddlemanSystem.com . By visiting our website, you accept and agree to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy. In particular, you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this privacy policy. 

Our goal is clear and prominent disclosure. 

If you do not understand any part of this privacy policy, please ask us to explain it to you by sending an e-mail to service (at) ArbitrageConspiracy.com / MiddlemanSystem.com / MiddlemanSystem.com (replacing the "(at)" with the "@" symbol and removing the spaces) with your question and wait for an answer from us before using this Website. If you do not want to use e-mail, you may also mail your questions to us at:

ArbitrageConspiracy.com / MiddlemanSystem.com  
1177 Branham Lane  
Suite 277  
San Jose, CA 95118  
USA

 **2\. Minors.**

We do not provide services or sell products to children. If you are below the age of 18, you may use our website only with the permission and active involvement of a parent or legal guardian. If you are a minor, please do not provide us or other website visitors with any personal information.

 **3\. Policy Is Part Of Our Terms And Conditions Of Use ("Terms of Service").**

Our privacy policy is part of, and subject to, our website's terms and conditions of use. You may view these terms and conditions by scrolling to the bottom of the page to view the link[](http://www.arbitrageconspiracy.com/site/info/terms-of-service).

 **4\. The Type Of Information We Collect From You.**

Like most places on the Internet, simply by visiting our website you automatically tell us certain information. This includes basic information such as your IP address, when you visited, the website from where you came prior to visiting us, the website where you go when you leave our website, your computer's operating system, and the type of web browser that you are using. Our website automatically records this basic information about you.

And like many other websites, we may use cookies. In plain English, this means information that our website's server transfers to your computer. This information can be used to track your session on our website. Cookies may also be used to customize our website content for you as an individual. If you are using one of the common Internet web browsers, you can set up your browser to either let you know when you receive a cookie or to deny cookie access to your computer.

We may also collect any data that you provide us by posting it at our website or by e-mail. You can always choose not to provide us with information. However, if you do withhold information, we may deny you access to some or all of our website's services and features.

Some transactions between you and our website may involve payment by credit card, debit card, checks, money orders, and/or third party online payment services. In such transactions, we will collect information related to the transaction as part of the course of doing business with you, including your billing address, telephone number, and other information related to the transaction.

When you visit this website, you may view advertisements posted on the site by Google or other companies. These advertising companies may collect information about you while you are visiting this website and other websites. They may use this data to show you advertisements on this website and elsewhere on the internet about products and services you might like. This website does not collect the information or control the content of the advertisements that you will see. You may be able to opt out of such advertising. To find out more about Google and its DoubleClick Dart cookie used to generate interest-based advertising, scroll to the bottom of the page to view the link. Your use of this website without opting out means that you understand and agree to data collection to provide you with interest-based advertising.

**5\. What We Do With Your Information.**

 **WE USE YOUR INFORMATION TO OPERATE OUR WEBSITE'S BUSINESS ACTIVITIES. FOR EXAMPLE, WE MAY USE THIS DATA TO CONTACT YOU ABOUT CHANGES TO OUR WEBSITE, NEW SERVICES, OR SPECIAL OFFERS, RESOLVE DISPUTES, TROUBLESHOOT ISSUES, AND ENFORCE OUR WEBSITE'S TERMS AND CONDITIONS.

WE MAY, IN OUR SOLE DISCRETION, PROVIDE INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO LAW ENFORCEMENT OR OTHER GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS FOR PURPOSES OF FRAUD INVESTIGATIONS, ALLEGED INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY INFRINGEMENT, OR ANY OTHER SUSPECTED ILLEGAL ACTIVITY OR MATTERS THAT MAY EXPOSE US TO LEGAL LIABILITY.

WE MAY, IN OUR SOLE DISCRETION, DISCLOSE AGGREGATE DATA AND INDIVIDUALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION ABOUT OUR WEBSITE'S VISITORS (INCLUDING YOU) TO ADVERTISERS OR OTHER THIRD PARTIES FOR MARKETING, PROMOTIONAL AND OTHER BUSINESS PURPOSES. BY USING THIS WEBSITE AND PROVIDING INFORMATION TO US IN THE PROCESS OF DOING SO, YOU ARE EXPRESSLY AGREEING TO OUR COLLECTION OF SUCH INFORMATION AND DISCLOSURE OF IT TO OTHERS. IF YOU DO NOT WANT SUCH INFORMATION DISCLOSED TO THIRD PARTIES, YOU SHOULD NOT USE THIS WEBSITE. 

IN ADDITION, WE MAY USE THIRD PARTY SUPPLIERS TO PROVIDE SERVICES ON OUR WEBSITE. IF A SUPPLIER WANTS TO COLLECT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, YOU WILL NOT BE NOTIFIED. HOWEVER, WE RESTRICT THE WAY THIRD PARTY SUPPLIERS CAN USE YOUR INFORMATION. THEY ARE NOT ALLOWED TO SELL OR GIVE YOUR INFORMATION TO OTHERS.

**

 **6\. User Names And Passwords.**

Your access to parts of our website may be protected by a user name and a password. Do not give your password to anyone. If you enter a section of our website that requires a password, you should log out when you leave. As a safety precaution, you should also close out of your web browser completely and re-open it before viewing other parts of the Internet.

 **7\. Your Use Of Information And Unsolicited Junk E-Mail.**

If you obtain personally identifiable information about another website user, you are not allowed to disclose this information to anyone else without the consent of the user and our consent too.  
We hate junk e-mail (Spam). Information you obtain from our website about us or other site users cannot be used by you or others to send unsolicited commercial e-mail or to send unsolicited commercial communications via our website's posting or other communication systems.

 **8\. Your Voluntary Disclosure Of Information To Third Parties Who Are Not Our Suppliers.**

You may choose to provide personal information to website visitors or other third parties who are not our suppliers. Please use caution when doing so. The privacy policies and customs of these third parties determine what is done with your information.

 **9\. Autoresponders.**

We may use autoresponders to communicate with you by e-mail. To protect your privacy, we use a verified opt-in system for such communications and you can always opt-out of such communications using the links contained in each autoresponder message. If you have difficulties opting out, you may contact us by sending an e-mail to service (at) ArbitrageConspiracy.com / MiddlemanSystem.com (replacing the "(at)" with the "@" symbol and removing the spaces), or sending us mail to the address listed below.

 **10\. Policy Changes.**

The terms of this policy may change from time to time. If such changes are made, we will notify you by a notice posted on our website's home page of the changes that have been made. If you disagree with the changes that have been made, please contact us (by e-mail, using a website contact form, or in writing by mail), and any changes made to this policy will not apply to information we have collected from you prior to making the changes.

If you are concerned about the topic covered by this policy, you should read it each time before you use our website. Any questions or concerns about this policy should be brought to our attention by sending an e-mail to service (at) ArbitrageConspiracy.com / MiddlemanSystem.com (replacing the "(at)" with the "@" symbol and removing the spaces) and providing us with information relating to your concern.

You may also mail your concerns to us at the following address:

ArbitrageConspiracy.com / MiddlemanSystem.com  
1177 Branham Lane Suite 277  
San Jose, CA 95118  
USA

 **12\. Changes in Our Business.**

If we sell or transfer this Website to a third party, we will take reasonable steps to protect your privacy consistent with this privacy policy. If we are sold to, transferred to, or merge with a third party, we will also take reasonable steps to protect your privacy consistent with this privacy policy. The steps taken to protect your privacy will be based on the website's privacy policy at the time we collected data from you.

 **13\. California Privacy Rights.**

If you are a California resident and our customer, Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.83 permits you to request certain information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To request this information, please send an e-mail to service (at) ArbitrageConspiracy.com / MiddlemanSystem.com (replacing the "(at)" with the "@" symbol and removing the spaces) or write us at the following address:

ArbitrageConspiracy.com / MiddlemanSystem.com  
1177 Branham Lane  
Suite 277  
San Jose, CA 95118  
USA

Please note that we are not based in California and only provide information requested as a courtesy to any California residents who are our customers. We do not consent to the jurisdiction of any federal, state, or local court within California. California law does not govern the rights between us. For more information about applicable law and the venue for dispute resolution, please read the website's terms of service by scrolling to the bottom of the page to view the link.

This policy was last updated on August 10, 2009.

Copyright © 2009 Law Office of Michael E. Young PLLC, and licensed for use by Great Era Holdings Ltd. at ArbitrageConspiracy.com / MiddlemanSystem.com. All Rights Reserved. No portion of this document may be copied or used by anyone other than the licensee without the express written permission of the copyright owner.
